<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="privacy">
        Treflor, (“Treflor”, “our”, “us” or “we”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy in connection with your use of our website, Treflor.com (the “Website(s)”), applications “Apps”) and other products, services and features thereof (the Website, the Apps and such other products, services and features are collectively referred to herein as the “Product” or “Products”, which may be updated from time-to-time at the sole discretion of Treflor). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) and any other documents referred to herein set forth the basis on which any personal information we collect from you, or that you provide to us, in connection with the Products will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal information and how we will collect, use and disclose your personal information.
    </string>
    <string name="info">
    We may collect and process the following information about you:"\n"

        - Personal information including, for example, your name, e-mail address, telephone, credit or debit card or other payment information, information about your usage of the Products and information collected by tracking technologies as further described below that may identify you as an individual or allow online or offline contact with you as an individual."\n"

        - Facebook profile information, such as name, email address, and Facebook ID, if you choose to log in to the Products through Facebook."\n"

        - Device Information such as operating system version, device type, and system performance information."\n"

        - Information collected via tracking technologies, as fully described in section 4.
    </string>
    <string name="security">
    The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at support@Treflor.com. Except as described under the “Disclosure of Your Information” section below, we do not provide your personal information to any third party without your specific consent.
    </string>

    <string name="tracking">
Treflor and our analytics partners, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts to enable a service to recognize your device so you don\'t have to provide the same information several times during one task, recognize that you may have already given a username and password so you don\'t need to do it for every web page requested, and measuring how many people are using services."\n"

    We use local storage technologies, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on the Products also use HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5."\n"

    We partner with third parties, such as Facebook and Google, to manage our advertising of the Products on other sites or platforms as well as across your other devices based on your past visits to our website. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities within the Products to deliver such advertising to you, such as retargeting ads. We currently do not respond to do-not-track signals. For more information about interest-based ads, including how to opt-out of having your web-browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. Please note that this does not opt you out of being served ads. You may continue to receive generic ads on these third party platforms. You may also opt out of receiving ads across devices by adjusting your ad preference in your Google account."\n"

    We use third party trackers to let us know when users have visited the Products by “clicking-through” our sponsored advertising or content hosted on third party platforms."\n"

    The Products use Google Analytics code to gather statistical information. Google Analytics sets cookies to help us accurately estimate the number of visitors to the Products and the volumes of usage of the Products. This is done to ensure that the Products are available when you want them and are fast. For more information on how Google Analytics processes this information, visit www.google.com/analytics.

    </string>
    <string name="personal_info">
All information you provide to us through the Products is stored on our secure servers located in the US. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology; all payment information is stored with our payment processor and is never stored on Treflor’ servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the Products, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone, and suggest that you change your password frequently. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to the Products; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.
</string>

    <string name="sign_in">
    You can log into our Products using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you to the option to post information about your activities on our Products or to your profile page to share with others within your network.
    </string>
    <string name="access">
    You may access your personal information at any time via an online account, or by emailing support@Treflor.com. To request the deletion of your personal data that we have on file please email us at support@Treflor.com. We will respond to your request in a reasonable timeframe.
    </string>

    <string name="uses">
    We use information held about you in the following ways:"\n"

        To ensure that content provided by the Products is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device."\n"

        To provide you with information, products or services related to Treflor that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, unless you have requested that we not provide this information."\n"

        To provide you with customer service communications."\n"

        To carry out our obligations arising from any agreements entered into between you and us."\n"

        To allow you to participate in interactive features of the Products, when you choose to do so."\n"

        To notify you about changes to the Products."\n"

        To understand your broad, non-specific geographic location to help us identify groups of users by general geographic market (such as zip code, state or country)."\n"

        To inform your Community about your registration and use of the Products."\n"

        To serve our advertisements to you through third party platforms, such as Facebook or Google, on other sites and apps or across your devices."\n"

        To provide you with the SMS Service."\n"

        We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them."\n"

        Details of transactions you carry out through the Products are used for the fulfillment of your Product orders."\n"

        Details of your visits to and interactions with the Products including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access."\n"

        If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or in-Product communication) with information about products and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you."\n"

        We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to companies that host advertisements on our behalf, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target."\n"

    We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries."\n"

    We may also disclose your personal information to third parties as follows:"\n"

        In some circumstances, based on your specific requests, we may need to disclose your personal information to a third party so that they can provide a service you have requested from such party, or fulfill a request for information from such party. An example of this is the SMS Service. It is the responsibility of any third party that you authorize to receive data to protect that information in accordance with applicable laws, and use it only to provide the services or information you have requested."\n"

        In some circumstances, we may disclose personal information that you have provided to Treflor to a third party that offers and/or provides goods or services complementary to our own, but only in cases where you have provided your consent, and where we have provided clear and conspicuous notice at the time the consent was communicated that your email address could be transferred to such other party for the purpose of initiating commercial electronic mail messages."\n"

        If Treflor’ service providers (like hosting, market analytics, and payment service providers) require this information to provide services to Treflor. Treflor requires each of its service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information disclosed."\n"

        In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets."\n"

        If Treflor or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets."\n"

        If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation such as to comply with a subpoena, bankruptcy proceedings, similar legal process, or in order to enforce or apply our agreements with you; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Treflor, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction."\n"

        With third parties, such as Facebook, in order to serve Treflor advertisements on such third party platforms.
    </string>

    <string name="policy_changes">
    We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by in-Product message, email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice in the Products prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
    </string>

    <string name="about">
        Treflor helps people explore the outdoors with the largest collection of detailed, hand-curated journey maps as well as journey reviews and photos crowdsourced from a community of in specially Sri Lanka."\n"
        Treflor has built the most complete, accurate dataset for off-road recreation ever, along with the easiest-to-use product suite that helps users find, customize, record and share outdoor activities and the largest and most active digital community of outdoor enthusiasts.
    </string>
</resources>